{
    "subject": "resource/Justin_R._Durban",
    "predicate": "ontology/instrument",
    "object": "resource/Guitar",
    "human_readable": "Justin R. Durban plays Guitar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9292986392974854,
            "question": "What instrument does Justin R. Durban play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9045510292053223,
            "question": "Is Justin R. Durban a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8772690296173096,
            "question": "Has Justin R. Durban received any awards for his guitar playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8693913221359253,
            "question": "Does Justin R. Durban play any other instruments besides Guitar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8693839907646179,
            "question": "What is Justin R. Durban's level of expertise in playing the Guitar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8676862120628357,
            "question": "Is Justin R. Durban a professional musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7886122465133667,
            "question": "Where has Justin R. Durban performed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7721579074859619,
            "question": "What is Justin R. Durban known for playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.723508894443512,
            "question": "What genre of music does Justin R. Durban likely play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6303064823150635,
            "question": "Has Justin R. Durban released any music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Justin R. Durban plays Guitar.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4185_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music does Justin R. Durban likely play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4185_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Justin R. Durban known for playing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4185_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where has Justin R. Durban performed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4185_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4185_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4185_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4185_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4185_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4185_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4185_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4185_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4185_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4185_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4185_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text documents do not mention Justin R. Durban playing the guitar.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`\n\nThe documents mention that Justin R. Durban was born on December 7th, 1977 in Memphis Tennessee and raised in the small town of Madisonville, Kentucky, but there is no mention of him playing the guitar. Additionally, his profession is mentioned as a composer and filmmaker, but not specifically as a guitarist."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information about Justin R. Durban playing the guitar. They discuss his background in graphic design, art studio, and theatre, as well as his work in music production for films such as \"Firecracker\" and \"Darkness.\" There is no mention of him playing a specific instrument like the guitar."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information in the provided context to suggest or indicate that Justin R. Durban plays the guitar.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Justin R. Durban playing guitar in the provided context information.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Justin R. Durban playing the guitar at all, but rather talks about his Graphic Design and Art studio background, Theatre minor, and work as a composer and filmmaker. There is no mention of him playing the guitar.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "None of the provided context information mentions Justin R. Durban playing guitar. The details focus on his background, education, move to Los Angeles, and work as a composer for films like \"Firecracker\" and \"Darkness,\" but do not include any information about him playing guitar.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}